<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">" List of Ancient Animals"</string>
    <string name="string_daftar_ras_hewan">Animal Race List</string>
    <string name="string_tekan_gambar_untuk_membuka_galeri">" (Press image to open gallery)"</string>
    <string name="string_american_mastodon_nama">American Mastodon</string>
    <string name="string_american_mastodon_asal">Amerika</string>
    <string name="string_american_mastodon_deskripsi">The height of the female elephant is 7 feet (2.1 meters) and the male is 10 feet (3 meters). It can weigh up to 6 tons, its length reaches 4.5 meters and its tusks are 2 meters long</string>
    <string name="string_amebelodon_asal">North Amerikaa</string>
    <string name="string_amebelodon_nama">Amebelodon</string>
    <string name="string_amebelodon_deskripsi">" The most prominent feature of Amebelodon is the lower tusk that is shaped like a spade. These two tusks are flat, flat and close together"</string>
    <string name="string_mammoth_berbulu_nama">Mammoth Berbulu</string>
    <string name="string_mammoth_berbulu_asal">Samudra Arktik</string>
    <string name="string_mammoth_berbulu_deskripsi">The woolly mammoth was last seen 4,000 years ago on a remote island in the Arctic Ocean. Humans have indeed lived side by side with mammoths. Unfortunately, early humans used to hunt mammoths to use their organs. For example, wearing fur as clothing or ivory as a tool for hunting.</string>
    <string name="string_deinotherium_nama">Deinotherium</string>
    <string name="string_deinotherium_asal">Afrika</string>
    <string name="string_deinotherium_deskripsi">Usually elephant tusks are curved upwards, in contrast to Deinotherium. This elephant tusk actually curves downwards and tends to be short.</string>
    <string name="string_palaeomastodon_nama">Palaeomastodon</string>
    <string name="string_palaeomastodon_asal">"North Afrika "</string>
    <string name="string_palaeomastodon_deskripsi">Menurut para ilmuwan, Palaeomastodon adalah kerabat dekat Moeritherium, salah satu nenek moyang gajah. Sepintas, wujudnya mirip dengan tapir yang kita kenal sekarang.</string>
    <string name="string_stegomastodon_nama">Stegomastodon</string>
    <string name="string_stegomastodon_asal">Amerika Selatan</string>
    <string name="string_stegomastodon_deskripsi">Stegomastodon elephants lived in the Late Pliocene to Modern, about 3 million to 10,000 years ago</string>
    <string name="string_andalgalornis_nama">Andalgalornis</string>
    <string name="string_andalgalornis_asal">Argentina</string>
    <string name="string_andalgalornis_deskripsi">" Andalgalornis is a giant predatory bird that lived during the Late Miocene, or about 23 million years ago."</string>
    <string name="string_titanis_nama">Titanis</string>
    <string name="string_titanis_asal">Amerika Selatan</string>
    <string name="string_titanis_deskripsi">Titanis became one of the birds that was quite feared during the Pliocene to Pleistocene, or about 3.1 million years ago and earned the nickname as the Terror Bird.</string>
    <string name="string_phorusracos_nama">Phorusracos</string>
    <string name="string_phorusracos_asal">Argentina</string>
    <string name="string_phorusracos_deskripsi">The animal, which has the Latin name Phorusracos longissimus, which means very long, has a height of 2.5 meters and a weight of 130 kg.</string>
    <string name="string_gastornis_nama">Gastornis</string>
    <string name="string_gastornis_asal">Eropa</string>
    <string name="string_gastornis_deskripsi">30 million years ago. Birds with the Latin name Gastornis gigantea generally preyed on small mammals that lived at that time. The height of which reached 2 meters made this bird the main predator at that time.</string>
    <string name="string_argentavis_nama">Argentavis</string>
    <string name="string_argentavis_asal">Argentina</string>
    <string name="string_argentavis_deskripsi">" Argentavis is the largest flying bird that has ever existed on earth, with a wingspan of 7 meters to 8 meters."</string>
    <string name="string_kelenken_nama">Kelenken</string>
    <string name="string_kelenken_asal">province of Rio Negro</string>
    <string name="string_kelenken_deskripsi">Kelenken became the largest flightless bird, from the Phorusrhacidae family that ever existed, with a skull length that has been found to be 71.6 cm.</string>
    <string name="string_lancetfish_nama">Lancetfish</string>
    <string name="string_lancetfish_asal">" The North Pole"</string>
    <string name="string_lancetfish_deskripsi">Lancetfish measure about 2 meters and can be found in many oceans except the poles. He also preys on smaller fish, squid and even his own.</string>
    <string name="string_arwana_nama">Arwana</string>
    <string name="string_arwana_asal">Asia,Afrika,and Australia\"</string>
    <string name="string_arwana_deskripsi">The magnificence of this beautifully colored animal can be seen up to two meters above the air to catch birds or bats</string>
    <string name="string_frilled_shark_nama">Frilled Shark</string>
    <string name="string_frilled_shark_asal">Outback Sea</string>
    <string name="string_frilled_shark_deskripsi">This deep-sea predator that existed in the Cretaceous period is still alive today.</string>
    <string name="string_sturgeon_nama">Sturgeon</string>
    <string name="string_sturgeon_asal">Rusia</string>
    <string name="string_sturgeon_deskripsi">The population of this fish is highly threatened due to uncontrolled hunting. This species can grow up to 6 meters. Sturgeons are also harmless to humans unless they feel threatened.</string>
    <string name="string_sawfish_nama">Sawfish</string>
    <string name="string_sawfish_asal">Outback Sea</string>
    <string name="string_sawfish_deskripsi">Also known as the saw shark. This marine predator also has a near-extinct status. In addition to the sea, Sawfish can also be found in rivers or creeks. Its size reaches 7 meters making it look like a shark.</string>
    <string name="string_coelacanthh_nama">Coelacanthh</string>
    <string name="string_coelacanthh_asal">Outback Sea</string>
    <string name="string_coelacanthh_deskripsi">This pet food is small fish and even small sharks. This fish is also commonly found in dark waters.</string>
    <string name="gajah">Elephant</string>
    <string name="burung">Fish</string>
    <string name="ikan">Bird</string>
</resources>